# Dániel Dénes



denes.daniel93@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/leinadsened



06301579501



https://leinadsened.github.io/

## Summary

Started a career change in early 2022 with 3 years working experience and an almost finished masters degree in chemical process engineering. So far I have finished Greenfox's junior software tester bootcamp and I'm looking forward for the automation tester bootcamp. I have experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python, and some familiarity with Java and C#.

## **Experience**



#### Chemist

Organofil Kft.

Sep 2018 - Aug 2019 (1 year)

**Technologist Assistant** 

Egis Pharmaceuticals PLC Feb 2017 - Aug 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Laboratory Technician

Egis Pharmaceuticals PLC Jun 2015 - Aug 2015 (3 months)

## **Education**



### **W** Green Fox Academy

Junior automata tesztelő Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Green Fox Academy

Junior szoftver tesztelő Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

112/120 credits completed, Process Engineering Jan 2019 - Jun 2022

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

Bachelor's degree, Chemical Engineering 2012 - 2018

## Skills

Software Testing • Manual Testing • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Python (Programming Language) • Microsoft Office • Research